## **SRILALITHA NOOKALA (SRI)**

Melbourne, Victoria, 3024

Phone: 0498800532| Email: srilalitha.ganti@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/srilalitha-nookala | GitHub: https://github.com/SrilalithaN |

Portfolio: https://srilalithan.github.io/Portfolio/

## Summary

A Full Stack Web Developer with a background in engineering and life-long dedication to learning. Recently got a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from Monash University with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. A passionate programmer with an aim to make applications to best engage my audience for an impactful user experience. A team player with good organization skills and an aim in delivering timely results.

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MySql, Sequelize, Handlebars.js

**Applications**: GitHub

## **Projects**

### **Tracking-Journal**

https://annanguyen1.github.io/Track-Journal/homepage.html https://github.com/AnnaNguyen1/Track-Journal

- Tracking Journal is an application for users to find parks around a certain radius for a given address and keep track of their experiences.
- Responsibilities: To design one of the pages in the application, style it, display current weather by fetching Weather API, and some added functionalities to refine the UI.
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript/jQuery/ Web-APIs

#### Warehouse On Wheels

https://github.com/SrilalithaN/warehouse-manager https://warehouse-manager-bootcamp.herokuapp.com/

- Warehouse on Wheels is a warehouse management system for second-hand car dealers.
- Responsibilities: To use Node.js and Express.js to create RESTful APIs. Used GET, POST, PUT, DELETE methods to retrieve,add,update and delete data.
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Node.js/Express.js/Sequelize/MySQL/Handlebars.js

## Workday-Scheduler

https://github.com/SrilalithaN/Workday-Schedulerhttps://srilalithan.github.io/Workday-Scheduler

- Workday-Scheduler is a day planner application. This application displays standard business hours where a user can make notes of their to-do tasks and save them.
- Sole Author
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Moment.js

#### Experience

## Sree Vijaya Durga Junior College Junior Lecturer

December 2017- April 2018 Rajahmundry, India

Volunteered as a Computer teacher for high-school students. Key Accomplishments:

- Effectively planned lessons and helped students gain theoretical and practical knowledge in computers for a class of 60 students
- Ensuring wholesome development of students by developing their confidence in the subject.
- Managing the classroom, grading examinations/practicals and guizzes
- Ensuring proper computer lab etiquettes are followed.
- Was a backup to the computer lab assistants and clerks for any computer-related help.
- Assisted two teams of three students each in their final project.

# Wyndham Little Buddies Toy Library Toy Library Session Assistant

November 2021 – December 2021 Melbourne, Australia

Volunteered as an admin assistant for the toy library Key Accomplishments:

- Effectively communicating with the families that enter the toy library.
- Ensuring that the returned toys are counted and cleaned and reshelved in a proper condition.

# Oxfam Australia Web Development Volunteer

December2021 – Present Melbourne, Australia

- Working in a team to redesign website for the organization.
- Managing the front-end of the website.

#### Education

Certificate of Full Stack Web Development: Monash University. Melbourne, Victoria

**Bachelor Of Electronics and Communication Engineering:** L.D.R.P – Institute of Technology and Research. Gandhinagar, India.